import fromCountry from '../activities/001_my-country/fromCountry'
import isNationality from '../activities/001_my-country/isNationality'
import possessiveCountry from '../activities/001_my-country/possessiveCountry'

import affirmativeToNegative from '../activities/002_cities/affirmativeToNegative'
import affirmativeToInterrogative from '../activities/002_cities/affirmativeToInterrogative'
import citiesShortAnswer from '../activities/002_cities/citiesShortAnswer'

import abilitiesToNegative from '../activities/003_abilities/abilitiesToNegative'
import abilitiesToInterrogative from '../activities/003_abilities/abilitiesToInterrogative'
import abilitiesShortAnswers from '../activities/003_abilities/abilitiesShortAnswers'

import homeAffirmative from '../activities/004_home-sweet-home/homeAffirmative'
import homeNegative from '../activities/004_home-sweet-home/homeNegative'
import homeInterrogative from '../activities/004_home-sweet-home/homeInterrogative'
import homeShort from '../activities/004_home-sweet-home/homeShort'

import occupationsArticle from '../activities/005_what-do-you-do/occupationsArticle'
import occupationsSentence from '../activities/005_what-do-you-do/occupationsSentence'
import occupationsNegative from '../activities/005_what-do-you-do/occupationsNegative'

import stuffS from '../activities/006_so-much-stuff/stuffS'
import stuffEs from '../activities/006_so-much-stuff/stuffEs'
import stuffY from '../activities/006_so-much-stuff/stuffY'
import stuffIrregular from '../activities/006_so-much-stuff/stuffIrregular'

import demonstrativeNear from '../activities/007_where-we-live/demonstrativeNear'
import demonstrativeFar from '../activities/007_where-we-live/demonstrativeFar'
import demonstrativeBoth from '../activities/007_where-we-live/demonstrativeBoth'
import demonstrativeSentence from '../activities/007_where-we-live/demonstrativeSentence'

import familyRewriteSingular from '../activities/008_meet-my-family/familyRewriteSingular'
import familyRewritePlural from '../activities/008_meet-my-family/familyRewritePlural'
import familyWho from '../activities/008_meet-my-family/familyWho'
import familyWhose from '../activities/008_meet-my-family/familyWhose'

import monthsAddAdjective from '../activities/009_who-and-when/monthsAddAdjective'
import weeksToNegative from '../activities/009_who-and-when/weeksToNegative'
import personGender from '../activities/009_who-and-when/personGender'
import personPlural from '../activities/009_who-and-when/personPlural'

import temporaryAffirmative from "../activities/010_its-only-temporary/temporaryAffirmative"
import temporaryToNegative from "../activities/010_its-only-temporary/temporaryToNegative"
import temporaryToInterrogative from "../activities/010_its-only-temporary/temporaryToInterrogative"
import temporaryToShort from "../activities/010_its-only-temporary/temporaryShort"

import soonAffirmative from '../activities/011_coming-soon/soonAffirmative'
import soonToNegative from '../activities/011_coming-soon/soonToNegative'
import soonToInterrogative from '../activities/011_coming-soon/soonToInterrogative'
import soonShort from '../activities/011_coming-soon/soonShort'

import againPlural from '../activities/012_again-and-again/againPlural'
import againSingular from '../activities/012_again-and-again/againSingular'
import againToBe from '../activities/012_again-and-again/againToBe'

import routineSingularNegative from '../activities/013_its-routine/routineSingularNegative'
import routinePluralNegative from '../activities/013_its-routine/routinePluralNegative'
import routineMixedNegative from '../activities/013_its-routine/routineMixedNegative'

import aboutTimeToInterrogative from '../activities/014_about-time/aboutTimeToInterrogative'
import aboutTimeQuestion from '../activities/014_about-time/aboutTimeQuestion'

import dietManyMuch from '../activities/015_diet/dietManyMuch'

import bingingAffirmative from '../activities/016_binging/bingingAffirmative'
import bingingNegative from '../activities/016_binging/bingingNegative'
import bingingInterrogative from '../activities/016_binging/bingingInterrogative'

import hungryAffirmative from '../activities/017_im-hungry/hungryAffirmative'
import hungryNegative from '../activities/017_im-hungry/hungryNegative'
import hungryInterrogative from '../activities/017_im-hungry/hungryInterrogative'

import mealTimeAffirmative from '../activities/018_meal-time/mealTimeAffirmative'
import mealTimeNegative from '../activities/018_meal-time/mealTimeNegative'
import mealTimeInterrogative from '../activities/018_meal-time/mealTimeInterrogative'

import dreamsAffirmative from '../activities/019_dreams/dreamsAffirmative'
import dreamsNegative from '../activities/019_dreams/dreamsNegative'
import dreamsInterrogative from '../activities/019_dreams/dreamsInterrogative'
import dreamsShort from '../activities/019_dreams/dreamsShort'

import lovedOnes from '../activities/020_loved-ones/lovedOnes'

import exceptionalDays from '../activities/021_exceptional-days/exceptionalDays'

import yesterdayDayOfTheWeek from '../activities/022_yesterday/yesterdayDayOfTheWeek'
import yesterdayRewrite from '../activities/022_yesterday/yesterdayRewrite'

import historyToNegative from '../activities/023_its_history/historyToNegative'
import historyToInterrogative from '../activities/023_its_history/historyToInterrogative'
import historyShort from '../activities/023_its_history/historyShort'

import diary from '../activities/024_my-diary/diary'

import changedAffirmative from '../activities/025_changed/changedAffirmative'
import changedNegative from '../activities/025_changed/changedNegative'
import changedInterrogative from '../activities/025_changed/changedInterrogative'
import changedShort from '../activities/025_changed/changedShort'

import unfinishedAffirmative from '../activities/026_unfinished/unfinishedAffirmative'
import unfinishedNegative from '../activities/026_unfinished/unfinishedNegative'
import unfinishedInterrogative from '../activities/026_unfinished/unfinishedInterrogative'

import interruptedWhen from '../activities/027_interrupted/interruptedWhen'
import interruptedWhile from '../activities/027_interrupted/interruptedWhile'

import sequencingAfterFirst from '../activities/028_sequencing/sequencingAfterFirst'
import sequencingAfterSecond from '../activities/028_sequencing/sequencingAfterSecond'
import sequencingAnd from '../activities/028_sequencing/sequencingAnd'
import sequencingThen from '../activities/028_sequencing/sequencingThen'

import planningAffirmative from '../activities/029_planning-ahead/planningAffirmative'
import planningNegative from '../activities/029_planning-ahead/planningNegative'
import planningInterrogative from '../activities/029_planning-ahead/planningInterrogative'

const data = [
    {
        title: 'My Country',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Put the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example:
                {
                    prompt: 'Portugal / John',
                    answer: 'He is from Portugal.'
                },
                getQuestion: fromCountry
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences about nationality based on the country and gender.',
                example: {
                    prompt: 'England / Michael',
                    answer: 'He is English.'
                },
                getQuestion: isNationality
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences about countries using personal adjectives.',
                example: {
                    prompt: 'Spain / Mario',
                    answer: 'His country is Spain.'
                },
                getQuestion: possessiveCountry
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Cities',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentence in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example:
                {
                    prompt: 'John is from Toronto.',
                    answer: "John isn't from Toronto."
                },
                getQuestion: affirmativeToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentence in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example:
                {
                    prompt: 'John is from Toronto.',
                    answer: "Is John from Toronto?"
                },
                getQuestion: affirmativeToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentence in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example:
                {
                    prompt: 'John is from Toronto.',
                    answer: "Is John from Toronto?"
                },
                getQuestion: citiesShortAnswer
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Abilities',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Bob can swim.',
                    answer: `Bob can't swim.`
                },
                getQuestion: abilitiesToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Bob can swim.',
                    answer: 'Can Bob swim?'
                },
                getQuestion: abilitiesToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write short answers to the questions. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Can Bob swim? / Affirmative',
                    answer: 'Yes, he can.'
                },
                getQuestion: abilitiesShortAnswers
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Home, Sweet Home',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences about existence in the affirmative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'two lamps in my bedroom.',
                    answer: 'There are'
                },
                getQuestion: homeAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences about existence in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'two lamps in my bedroom.',
                    answer: "There aren't"
                },
                getQuestion: homeNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences about existence in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'two lamps in you bedroom?',
                    answer: 'Are there'
                },
                getQuestion: homeInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write short answers about existence. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Are there two lamps in your bedroom?',
                    answer: 'Yes, there are.'
                },
                getQuestion: homeShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'What do you do?',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences with the correct indeterminate article. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael is __ doctor.',
                    answer: 'a'
                },
                getQuestion: occupationsArticle
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / doctor',
                    answer: 'Michael is a doctor'
                },
                getQuestion: occupationsSentence
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / engineer / doctor',
                    answer: 'Michael is an Engineer, he is a doctor.'
                },
                getQuestion: occupationsNegative
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'So much stuff',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write the plural form of the words given. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'horse',
                    answer: 'horses'
                },
                getQuestion: stuffS
            },
            {
                description: 'Write the plural form of the words given. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'pass',
                    answer: 'passes'
                },
                getQuestion: stuffEs
            },
            {
                description: 'Write the plural form of the words given. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'fly',
                    answer: 'flies'
                },
                getQuestion: stuffY
            },
            {
                description: 'Write the plural form of the words given. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'child',
                    answer: 'children'
                },
                getQuestion: stuffIrregular
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Where we live',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences with the correct demonstrative pronoun for proximity. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'is a hospital.',
                    answer: 'This'
                },
                getQuestion: demonstrativeNear
            },
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences with the correct demonstrative pronoun for distance. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'is a hospital.',
                    answer: 'That'
                },
                getQuestion: demonstrativeFar
            },
            {
                description: 'Complete the sentences with the correct demonstrative pronoun. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'is a hospital. (near)',
                    answer: 'This'
                },
                getQuestion: demonstrativeBoth
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompt. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'hospital. (near)',
                    answer: 'This is a hospital.'
                },
                getQuestion: demonstrativeSentence
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Meet my family',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences using the genitive case. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John: "Michael is my brother."',
                    answer: "Michael is John's brother."
                },
                getQuestion: familyRewriteSingular,
                amount: 6
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences using the genitive case. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John and Paul: "Michael is my brother."',
                    answer: "Michael is John and Paul's brother."
                },
                getQuestion: familyRewritePlural,
                amount: 6
            },
            {
                description: 'Write questions about family. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John / Brother',
                    answer: "Who is John's brother?"
                },
                getQuestion: familyWho
            },
            {
                description: 'Write questions about family. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John / Brother',
                    answer: "Whose brother is John?"
                },
                getQuestion: familyWhose
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Who and When',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentence adding the adjective. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'October is a month. / rainy',
                    answer: 'October is a rainy month.'
                },
                getQuestion: monthsAddAdjective
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form, adding the adjective. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Sunday is a day. / bad',
                    answer: "Sunday isn't a bad day."
                },
                getQuestion: weeksToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences with the different person. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John is a good person. Mary',
                    answer: "Mary is a good person."
                },
                getQuestion: personGender
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences with the different people. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John is a good person. Mary and Josh',
                    answer: "Mary and Josh are good people."
                },
                getQuestion: personPlural
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "It's only temporary",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write a sentence based on the prompt. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John / Study',
                    answer: 'John is studying English this year.'
                },
                getQuestion: temporaryAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Sunday is a day. / bad',
                    answer: "Sunday isn't a bad day."
                },
                getQuestion: temporaryToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences with the different person. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John is a good person. Mary',
                    answer: "Mary is a good person."
                },
                getQuestion: temporaryToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences with the different people. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John is a good person. Mary and Josh',
                    answer: "Mary and Josh are good people."
                },
                getQuestion: temporaryToShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: 'Coming soon',
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Go to England next year',
                    answer: 'Michael will go to England next year.'
                },
                getQuestion: soonAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael will go to England next year.',
                    answer: "Michael won't go to England next year."
                },
                getQuestion: soonToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael will go to England next year.',
                    answer: 'Will Michael go to England next year?'
                },
                getQuestion: soonToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Will Michael go to England next year? (affirmative)',
                    answer: 'Yes, he will.'
                },
                getQuestion: soonShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Again and again",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael and Josh / never / watch TV / Wednesday',
                    answer: 'Michael and Josh never watch TV on Wednesdays.'
                },
                getQuestion: againPlural
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / never / watch TV / Wednesday',
                    answer: 'Michael never watches TV on Wednesdays.'
                },
                getQuestion: againSingular,
                amount: 6
            },
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / never / sad / Wednesday',
                    answer: 'Michael is never sad on Wednesdays.'
                },
                getQuestion: againToBe
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "It's just routine",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael plays tennis at 7am.',
                    answer: "Michael doesn't play tennis at 7am."
                },
                getQuestion: routineSingularNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael and Josh play tennis at 7am.',
                    answer: "Michael and Josh don't don't play tennis at 7am."
                },
                getQuestion: routinePluralNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael and Josh play tennis at 7am.',
                    answer: "Michael and Josh don't don't play tennis at 7am."
                },
                getQuestion: routineMixedNegative,
                amount: 6
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "About time",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write these sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael watches TV at 7pm.',
                    answer: 'Does Michael watch TV at 7pm?'
                },
                getQuestion: aboutTimeToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write questions based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / watch TV',
                    answer: 'What time does Michael watch TV?'
                },
                getQuestion: aboutTimeQuestion,
                amount: 6
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "It's a Diet",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'sandwich / week',
                    answer: 'How many sandwiches do you eat in a week?'
                },
                getQuestion: dietManyMuch,
                amount: 6
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Binging",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write affirmative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Sandwich',
                    answer: 'Michael eats a lot of sandwiches.'
                },
                getQuestion: bingingAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write negative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Sandwich',
                    answer: "Michael doesn't eat many sandwiches."
                },
                getQuestion: bingingNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write interrogative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Sandwich',
                    answer: 'Does Michael eat many sandwiches?'
                },
                getQuestion: bingingInterrogative
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "I'm hungry",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write affirmative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'eggs',
                    answer: 'There are some eggs in the fridge.'
                },
                getQuestion: hungryAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write negative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'eggs',
                    answer: "There aren't any eggs in the fridge."
                },
                getQuestion: hungryNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write interrogative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'eggs',
                    answer: "Are There any eggs in the fridge?"
                },
                getQuestion: hungryInterrogative
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Meal Time",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write affirmative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Cake',
                    answer: 'Michael would like some cake.'
                },
                getQuestion: mealTimeAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write negative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Cake',
                    answer: "Michael wouldn't like some cake."
                },
                getQuestion: mealTimeNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write interrogative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / Cake',
                    answer: 'Would Michael like some cake?'
                },
                getQuestion: mealTimeInterrogative
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Dream On",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write affirmative sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / work from home',
                    answer: 'If possible, Michael would work from home.'
                },
                getQuestion: dreamsAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael would work from home, if possible.",
                    answer: "Michael wouldn't work from home, if possible."
                },
                getQuestion: dreamsNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'If possible, Michael would work from home.',
                    answer: 'If possible, would Michael work from home?'
                },
                getQuestion: dreamsInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write short answers to the questions. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "If possible, would Michael work from home? (Affirmative)",
                    answer: 'Yes, he would.'
                },
                getQuestion: dreamsShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Loved ones",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences using objective pronouns. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael likes Jessica.',
                    answer: 'Michael likes her.'
                },
                getQuestion: lovedOnes
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Exceptional days",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Michael / never / play tennis / watch TV',
                    answer: 'Michael never plays tennis. Today, he is watching TV.'
                },
                getQuestion: exceptionalDays
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Yesterday",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentence in the past tense. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John studies English.',
                    answer: 'John studied English.'
                },
                getQuestion: yesterdayRewrite
            },
            {
                description: 'Write past sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:',
                example:
                {
                    prompt: 'Sunday / Tom / play tennis',
                    answer: 'On Sunday, Tom played tennis.'
                },
                getQuestion: yesterdayRewrite
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "It's history",
        activities: [
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the negative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John danced salsa three days ago.',
                    answer: "John didn't dance salsa three days ago."
                },
                getQuestion: historyToNegative
            },
            {
                description: 'Re-write the sentences in the interrogative form. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'John danced salsa three days ago.',
                    answer: "Did John dance salsa three days ago?"
                },
                getQuestion: historyToInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: 'Write short answers to the questions. Follow the example:',
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: 'Did John dance salsa three days ago? (Affirmative)',
                    answer: "Yes, he did.."
                },
                getQuestion: historyShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "My diary",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Answer the question based with the information in brackets. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "When did Michael buy the TV? (two days)",
                    answer: "Michael bought the TV two days ago."
                },
                getQuestion: diary
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Changed",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past form. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "John is happy today.",
                    answer: "John was happy yesterday."
                },
                getQuestion: changedAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past form. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "John isn't happy today.",
                    answer: "John wasn't happy yesterday."
                },
                getQuestion: changedNegative
            },
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past form. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Is John happy today?",
                    answer: "Was John happy yesterday?"
                },
                getQuestion: changedInterrogative
            },
            {
                description: "Answer the question with the appropriate short answer:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Was John happy yesterday? (Affirmative)",
                    answer: "Yes, he was."
                },
                getQuestion: changedShort
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Unfinished",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past tense. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Daniel is singing in the shower.",
                    answer: "Daniel was singing in the shower."
                },
                getQuestion: unfinishedAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past tense. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Daniel isn't singing in the shower.",
                    answer: "Daniel wasn't singing in the shower."
                },
                getQuestion: unfinishedNegative
            },
            {
                description: "Re-write the sentences in the past tense. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Is Daniel singing in the shower?",
                    answer: "Was Daniel singing in the shower?"
                },
                getQuestion: unfinishedInterrogative
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Interrupted",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Josh / watch TV / Lisa / sleep in bed",
                    answer: "Josh was watching TV while Lisa was sleeping in bed."
                },
                getQuestion: interruptedWhile
            },
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Josh / watch TV / Lisa / open the door",
                    answer: "Josh was watching TV when Lisa opened the door."
                },
                getQuestion: interruptedWhen
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Sequencing",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael eat pasta / take a picture",
                    answer: "Michael ate pasta and took a picture."
                },
                getQuestion: sequencingAnd
            },
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael eat pasta / take a picture",
                    answer: "Michael ate pasta, then he took a picture."
                },
                getQuestion: sequencingThen
            },
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael eat pasta / take a picture",
                    answer: "After he ate pasta, Michael took a picture."
                },
                getQuestion: sequencingAfterFirst
            },
            {
                description: "Write sentences based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael eat pasta / take a picture",
                    answer: "Michael took a picture after he ate pasta."
                },
                getQuestion: sequencingAfterSecond
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        title: "Planning ahead",
        activities: [
            {
                description: "Write future plans based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael / play soccer / Friday",
                    answer: "Michael is going to play soccer on Friday."
                },
                getQuestion: planningAffirmative
            },
            {
                description: "Write negative future plans based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael / play soccer / Friday",
                    answer: "Michael isn't going to play soccer on Friday."
                },
                getQuestion: planningNegative
            },
            {
                description: "Write future plans based on the prompts. Follow the example:",
                example: 
                {
                    prompt: "Michael / play soccer / Friday",
                    answer: "Is Michael going to play soccer on Friday?"
                },
                getQuestion: planningInterrogative
            }
        ]
    },
]

export default data;


// {
//     title: ,
//     activities: [
//         {
//             description: "",
//             example: 
//             {
//                 prompt: "",
//                 answer: ""
//             },
//             getQuestion: null
//         }
//     ]
// },